Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities records, 1960-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 1: Amenity Resources/Quality of Life, 1973-2011; (38 boxes)
  - Key Issues and Trends for Design, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Kingsport Tennessee Branding Charrette, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Landscape, Aesthetics, and Public Policy, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Learning from Europe Study Tour, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Learning from Europe Study Tour, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Livability, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Livability Clearinghouse -- Animation, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Livability Clearinghouse -- Cultural Planning, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Livability Clearinghouse -- Open Space, Parks & Recreation, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Livability Clearinghouse -- Open Space, Parks & Recreation, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Livable City Revisited: Is There Anything Really New about New Urbanization? --Conference Program, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Living Downtowns: The Heart of Our City, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lloyds Row Charrette, Lloyds Row Townhouses, Duke Street, Alexandria, Virginia, May, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Local Government and the Arts, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Luce Report, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Luce Report, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Main Street News, Putting the Arts to Work for Downtown, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Management of Historic Maritime Resources, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Meanjin: The Creative City, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Memphis Arts Places as Art Charrette Summary Report and Workbook, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Memphis Arts Places as Art Charrette Summary Report and Workbook, 2998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Metropolis Now, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Minneapolis Beautiful Initiative, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Minnesota State Capitol Mall Animation Study, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Minnesota State Capitol Mall Animation Study, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota State Capitol Mall Animation Study, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Minnesota's State Capitol Mall: Minnesota's Front Yard, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Monumentum, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Movie Palaces: Renaissance and Reuse, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Models Relevant to Strategic Parks Planning Initiative, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Natural and Scenic Resources, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Nautical Archaeology, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Negotiating for Amenities: Zoning and Management Tools that Build Livable Cities, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - New Idea Corp, Broad Street Corridor, Richmond, Virginia Final Report, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - New Idea Corp, Broad Street Corridor, Richmond, Virginia Final Report, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Old Post Office: Staff Report to Nancy Hanks, Chairman, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Orlando Arts Forum Reports, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Parking Structures in Urban Design, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Parks and Recreation Leadership Forum, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Partners and Underwater Archaeology, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Partners and Underwater Archaeology, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Partners for Livable Places Fourth Annual Meeting: Animation: New Life for City Centers, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Partners for Livable Places Preservation News Supplement -- National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Partners for Livable Places Study Tour to Stockholm on Architectural Design Competitions, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Partners for Livable Places Technical Assistance Services for Communities, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Partners' Cultural Planning Policy Workshop, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Partnerships for Prosperity: Museums and Economic Development, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Photography for Graphic Designers, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Placemaking in Australia, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Places as Art, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Places as Art Charrette in Glendale, California, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Places as Art Charrette in Glendale, California, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Poland's Commitment to Its Past: A Report on Two Study Tours; An Issue Paper, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Press Response to the First Federal Design Assembly, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Pride in Place, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of Cultural Planning Conference, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Profitability and Design Management, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Public Art, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Public Art Placemaking Strategies, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Public Art Placemaking Strategies, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Public Sector Designers, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Public Service Design Abroad, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Quality of Life and Amenities as Urban Investment, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Raising the Standards- The Federal Graphic Improvement Program 1972-1980, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Reassessing How We Invest in our Cities, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Rebuilding American Communities: Reinvestment by Design - A Collection of Best Practices, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Rebuilding American Communities: Reinvestment by Design - A Collection of Best Practices, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Rebuilding American Communities: Reinvestment by Design - A Collection of Best Practices, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations to the Salisbury Wicomico Arts Council for the Boulevard Theater Renovation, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations to the Salisbury Wicomico Arts Council for the Boulevard Theater Renovation, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations to the Salisbury Wicomico Arts Council for the Boulevard Theater Renovation, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Recycling Historic Railroad Stations - A Citizens Manual & Technical Supplement, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Report on Parks and Recreation Department, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Report on the Amenity Planning Workshop; Columbus, Ohio, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    folder 1 of 7
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    folder 2 of 7
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    folder 3 of 7
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    folder 4 of 7
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    folder 5 of 7
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    folder 6 of 7
  - Report on the Foley Project Dallas Center for Arts and Culture Study, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    folder 7 of 7
  - Report on Visit to Sacramento - August 30 - September 1, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Report to the Mobile, Alabama Arts Council--Responses and Recommendations from the Community Assessment/Focus Group Meetings, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Reports Resulting from Sacramento, California's Participation in the Shaping Growth in American Communities Program, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for an individual in Garland, TX on Public Art: Commissioning and Funding Strategies, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for an individual in Philadelphia on Multi-Use Arts Facilities, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for individual member of Partners on Downtown Animation Strategies, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Project Green of Louisville, KY on Community involvement in landscape development strategies., 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for the City of Raleigh, NC on Visual Environment of Highways, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for the City of Vancouver, Canada on Cultural Amenities and Downtown Revitalization, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for the director of the Inner-Arts Program, National Endowment for the Arts, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for the Director of the Locals Program on the adaptive re-use of school buildings as cultural and arts centers, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for the University of Wisconsin in Madison, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Townscape Institute, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Research by the Livability Clearinghouse undertaken for Urban Development, City of Lincoln on Design Guidelines., 1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Research Memorandum for Chattanooga on Research Finding on Outdoor Interactive Fountains, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Resource Materials for the Downtown Live Program of City as a Stage of Washington, DC, the Meyer Foundation Project, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Resources and Materials from the Cultural Summit Strategy of the Federal City Council, Washington, DC 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Resources and Materials from the Cultural Summit Strategy of the Federal City Council, Washington, DC 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Response to the Economics of Amenity Program, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Reusing Railroad Stations/Volume II, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Sacramento Agenda 1989 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Salisbury, Maryland Workbook Portfolio, April 2002 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Sculpture, Picnicing, Jogging and Nature Studies, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Second Federal Design Assembly: The Design Reality, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Selected Readings on Public Art, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sense of Place, A Place for People, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Shaping Growth in American Communities: Report to Sacramento, California, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Site Analysis for Federal Offices in New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Smart City, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Soul of Pueblo: Preserving Central Pueblo's Culture through the Planning and Design Process, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Sourcebook: Economic Impact of the Arts, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Space and Nature: Practical Aesthetics, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Space for Dance, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Space for Dance, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Space for Dance, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Speech by Paul Goldberger at Partners' 25th Anniversary Celebration, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - State Arts Agency Design Activity, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - State Shipwreck Management, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - State Shipwreck Management, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Statistical Profile of Design Professions, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Strategic Parks Planning Initiative Idea Paper, first draft, The Community Design Center of Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Strategies for Maximizing the Value of Underwater Archaeology: Conference Report, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Strategies for Maximizing the Value of Underwater Archaeology: Conference Report, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Study for the Pennsylvania Avenue Development Commission on Animation, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Summary Report from the Design Arts Program, Facilities for the Arts Workshop November 17th - 18th, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - The Arts Edge: Revitalizing Economic Life in California Cities Through the Arts, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - The Arts in Found Places, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - The City and the Arts, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - The Economic Impact of the Arts, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - The Invisible City: An Issue of Design Quarterly 1986-87, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - The Need for Architectural Improvement in Design of Federal Buildings, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - The Planning and Administration of Design Competitions, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - The Presidential Design Awards 1984 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - The Role of Arts in Urban Economic Development, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Thoughts on Design Advocacy Project, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Tools for Leadership: Building Cultural Partnerships, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Urban Amenities: Linking Livability and Economic Development, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Urban Cultural Policy, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Urban Impact of Federal Policy, Purview of the Rand Study, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Urban Impact of Federal Policy, Purview of the Rand Study, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Urban Land Institute Panel - Downtown Orlando, FL, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Urban Parks and Open Space, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Urban Waterfront Action Group:Findings and Recommendations, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Value of the Arts, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Viewed from the Road, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Visit to Arkansas, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Want more Business and Industry? Make your Community Livable, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Waterfront Planning and Design Guidelines, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Way to Go: The Benefits of Quality Design in Transportation, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - What Makes Cities Livable, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - What Makes Cities Livable: Learning from Abroad Winning Designs, the Competition Renaissance, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - White Oak Findings: Developing a Public Policy Framework, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Wingspread Conference on Natural and Scenic Resources in American Community, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Zoning and Building Ordinances & Financial and Management Strategies for Urban Amenities: A Preliminary Survey, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Series 2: Community Development, 1960-2011; (24 boxes)
  Series 2 contains resources gathered by Partners for Livable Communities relevant to their various initiatives and programs.
  - A Blueprint for Action: Developing a Livable Community for All Ages, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Abandoned Properties, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Abandoned Properties, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Abandoned Properties, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Abandoned Properties, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Abandoned Properties, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Abandoned Properties, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Adapting Existing Neighborhoods: Naturally Occurring Retirement Communities as Platforms for Aging in Place, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Affordable Housing Portfolio, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Aging in Place, 2001 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Aging in Place in the 21st Century: A Blueprint for Change, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Aging in Place Initiative Best Practices, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Aging in Place Initiative Newsletter: Vol 1, Issue 1, Fall 2005 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Aging in Place Technical Assistance Guide, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Aging in Place: 2011 Portfolio Highlights (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Aging in Place: An Imperative Whose Time Has Come, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Aging in Place: Is it Possible in Sprawl? Creating Livable Communities for All, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Aging in Place: Issue Briefing and Resource Support Guide, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Aging in Place: Making Communities more Livable for Older Adults, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Aging in Place: Making Communities more Livable for Older Adults (new version), 2007 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Aging in Place: Solutions to a Crisis in Housing and Care Neighborhood Reinvestment Corporation, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Aging in Place: Strategies to Help the Elderly Stay in Revialized Neighberhoods, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Aging Summit 2008 Conclusions and Recommendations (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - America Today: Success, but for whom?, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - American Community, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science: Revitalizing the Industrial City, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Arlington County - Building Communities through Technology, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Arts Edge, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Audit 2007 (Chapter 1: Creating Livable Communities) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Background materials for workshop on Livable Communities for All, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Best Practices: A compendium of ideas and models for improving livability., 2001 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Best Practices: A compendium of ideas and models for improving livability., 2001 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Better Community Catalog: A Sourcebook of Ideas, People, and Strategies for Improving the Place Where You Live, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Beyond Shelter: Building Communities of Opportunity, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Bibliography: Enviornmental Mediation and Dispute Resolution, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - BIDs in Cleveland Establishing a Business Improvement District, A Step-by-Step Procedures Manual, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - BIDs in Cleveland Establishing a Business Improvement District, A Step-by-Step Procedures Manual, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - BIDs in Cleveland Establishing a Business Improvement District, A Step-by-Step Procedures Manual, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - BIDs in Cleveland Establishing a Business Improvement District, A Step-by-Step Procedures Manual, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Big Projects for Great Cities: 25 Projects Which Shape Up Their Area, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Blueprint 2000: A Framework for Building Tomorrow's Communities, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Blueprint 2000: A Framework for Building Tomorrow's Communities, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint 2000: A Framework for Building Tomorrow's Communities, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint 2000: Communities for the 21st Century Conference Guide, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint 2000: Communities for the 21st Century Conference Guide, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint 2000: Communities for the 21st Century Conference Guide, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Blueprint 2000: Communities for the 21st Century Conference, Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Building Livable Communities Through Transportation, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Building Tomorrow's Economy The Michigan Legislative & Business Leaders Public Policy Forum, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Business Improvement Districts: Taxation with Representation, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Challenges and Priorities: Local Solutions to National Problems, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Challenging Sprawl: Organizational Response to a National Problem, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Chattanooga: A Time for Change - Issues, Alternatives, Strategies to Improve Urban Livability, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Cities: The Forces that Shape Them, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - City of Salem, Massachusetts Downtown Retail and Cultural District Strategic Action Plan, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - City Options: Architecture and Environmental Art, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Cleveland City Club Forum, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Communities of All Ages, Final Report, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Community Schools Workshop Concept Paper, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Conference on Neighborhood Conservation: Revitalization by Design, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Conference on Neighborhood Conservation: Revitalization by Design, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Conserving Europe's 2000-year Heritage: Some Hints for an Urban America, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Continuing to Serve Livability for America's Future, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Creating a Livable City: Making Downtown San Diego Work, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Creating a livable Richmond Metro Area for All Ages, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Creating Globally Competitive Communities - Industrial Week, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Creating Globally Competitive Communities - MIS Report, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Creating Livable Communities for All, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Creating Livable Communities - Joint Venture for Collaborating for Livable Communities, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Creating Livable Environments for Work and Play, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Creating the Globally Competitive Community, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Crossing the Line: Developing a Livable Tampa Bay Region for All Age - Workshop Packet, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Designing the Livable Community, 1995 Workbook (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Designing the Livable Community, 1995 Workbook (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Developing a Livable Arizona for All Ages: Workshop Report Two, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Developing a Livable Arizona for All Ages: Workshop Report Two, 2007 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Developing a Livable Centralina Region for All Ages: Workshop Report Six, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Developing a Livable San Antonio Metro Region for All Ages, 2009 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Developing a Livable San Diego County for All Ages: Workshop Report Three, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Development Strategy for East Perth: An Outline of Discussions, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Downtown Redevelopment Research for the Lowertown Development Corporation, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Drug Issue: Thirty Best Practices for Drug Prevention, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Empowerment Zone Communities Technical Assistance Project Workbook, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Energy and Livability Linkages: Issues and Best Practices, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Energy Working Paper, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Engaging Older Adults Through Arts and Culture: Developing a Livable Chicago for All Ages, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Enhancing Lifelong Learning: Developing a Livable San Diego County for all Ages, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise at Home for Progress at Large: The Economics of Sustainability, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Environment Strategy America 1994/1995: The Way Forward (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Initiative Feasibility Study - Phase II Report, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Urban Planning, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Family Investment Strategies: Improving the Lives of Children and Communities., 1994 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Farmers' Markets: A Community Amenity, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Federal Department of Housing and Urban Development: Building Communities Together Resource Binder, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Federal Department of Housing and Urban Development: Building Communities Together Resource Binder, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Federal Programs for Neighborhood Conservation, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Final Report About Property Abandonment, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Final report of the Livability Definition for Communities for all ages, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Finding Funding on the Web: Tips for Internet Grantseeking, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Free the Children: Breaking the Cycle of Poverty, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - From Lessons to Actions, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Governing Magazine Insert: A Blueprint for Action, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Graffiti & Vandalism Anthology, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Graffiti and Vandalism: What's the Solution? What's the Problem?, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Guide to Neighborhood Ecology, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Hartford Connecticut Cultural Planning Charrette Executive Summary, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Hartford Connecticut Cultural Planning Charrette Executive Summary, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Hartford Connecticut Cultural Planning Charrette Executive Summary, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Hartford Connecticut Cultural Planning Charrette Executive Summary, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Heritage and Successful Town Regeneration, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Highbury Initiative Center City Challenge Symposium, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Hobbs Improvement Task Force Memo, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Hobbs, New Mexico: Creating a Great Good Place Summary Report, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Housing: Symbol, Structure, Site, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 7)